<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MIU CV Builder</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Home</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    //About Me
    <string name="about_me_personalInfo">Highly motivated and technically skilled Java developer with 3 years of hands on experience solving complex software
problems built to specification using best practices. An additional 4 years of civil engineering experience. Excellent skills in
implementing modern technologies such as Java, Spring, Spring boot, Hibernate, JPA, JavaScript, jQuery, RESTFUL API,
MySQL and MongoDB ensuring use of industry best standards. Knowledgeable in Agile/Scrum based SDLC methodologies.
Expert team player focused on maximizing production in minimum time and minimum cost.</string>
    <string name="weakness">I can be too critical of myself. A pattern I’ve noticed throughout my career is that I often feel I could have done more, even if objectively,
        I’ve done well. Earlier in my career, this led to burnout and negative self-talk. One solution I’ve implemented over the last three years is to actively pause and celebrate my achievements.
        Not only has this helped my own self-esteem, but it has also helped me genuinely appreciate and recognize my team and other support systems.</string>
    <string name="strength">I’m thorough and tenacious. When I’m on a project, I keep track of the details. Because I have a comprehensive understanding of the components,
        I can spot the essentials and rigorously advocate for them to meet deadlines. I regularly see this reflected in my peer and management feedback.</string>
    <string name="education">Master of Science in Computer Science \n\n
(Completed Course Studies, Graduating Dec 2020) \n\n
Maharishi International University – Fairfield, Iowa\n\n
Key Courses: Fundamental Programming Practices, Modern Programming Practices, Web Application Programming,
Web Application Architecture, Modern Web Application, Advanced Software development, Software Engineering,
Algorithm, Enterprise Architecture, Database Management System, Machine learning. \n\n
Bachelor of Science in Engineering\n\n
University Of Asmara, Eritrea.</string>

    <string name="hobbies">
        soccer\nn
        volleyBall\nn

    </string>


</resources>